- La, la, la, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la, la
La, la, la, la, la, la!
- Come on Jan, play the tape!
You gonna let us
listen to it anyway!
- La, la, la, la, la, la, la!
(grunts)
- Janny, listen to us
when we talking to you!
- La, la, la, la, la, la.
- I know you hear us!
What'chu think you
all that or somethin'?
- See, no, I don't
think I'm all that
you think I'm all that
that's why you
all on this, okay?
(Group moaning)
- Thank you!
- Janet, Janet, Janet?
- What, what?
- Don't play.
- [Group] (laughing)
- Thank you, baby,
thank you, Omar!
- Don't listen to him, please?
Can we hear it?
- No.
- I don't know what'chu
guys are talkin' about,
but Jan I been
meanin' to tell you
that your hair has
been looking so fie--
- Oh!
(group chuckling)
- Don't do it,
don't do it, honey!
- Aw, man!
- Now, wait now!
I'll play this tape when I'm
ready to play the tape, okay?
- [Group] (laughing)
- Okay, I'm ready
(laughing)
- Boo, what side?
- Side A, Boo!
- Huh?
- Side A!
- Pumpa, boo, pumpa!
- [Man] (laughing)
- Loud, honey,
- [Janet] Pumpa!
- Now she wants
everybody to hear
- [Group] Pumpa,
pumpa! (laughing)
- All right, you better
come with it now
- You know it is!
(high pitched laughter)
- [Man] How's it start, baby?
(laughing)
♪ Like a moth to a flame,
burned by the fire ♪
- [Woman] Oh no, here we go
- [Man] Tryin'a get deep with us
♪ My love is blind, can't
you see my desire? ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
(group humming to the beat)
- [Group] Go Janet, go Janet.
- [Man] Yo Tish,
what are you doing?
- [Janet] Tish?!
- Yo, this is slammin'
- Come on, Tish!
♪ Like a moth to a flame,
burned by the fire ♪
♪ [Male Singer]
That's the way lo-- ♪
♪ My love is blind, can't
you see my desire? ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ Like a moth to a flame,
burned by the fire ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way, that's the way ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ My love is blind,
can't you see my desire ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way, that's the way ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ Come with me don't you worry ♪
♪ I'm gonna make you crazy ♪
♪ I'll give you the
time of your life ♪
♪ I'm gonna take you places ♪
♪ You've never been before ♪
♪ You'll be so happy
that you came ♪
♪ Ooh I'm gonna take you there ♪
(ooh)
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way love goes ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ That's the way ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's the way ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ Desire ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way, that's the way ♪
♪ Don't mind if
I light candles ♪
♪ I like to watch us playin' ♪
♪ Baby I've got
on what you like ♪
♪ Come closer baby closer ♪
♪ Reach out and feel my body ♪
♪ I'm gonna give
you all my love ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's the way ♪
♪ Oh sugar don't you hurry ♪
♪ You've got me here all night ♪
♪ Just close your eyes
and hold on tight ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way, that's the way ♪
♪ Oh baby don't
stop don't stop ♪
♪ Go deeper, baby, deeper ♪
♪ You feel so good
I'm gonna cry ♪
♪ Oh I'm gonna take you there ♪
(ooh)
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ That's the way love
goes, and goes, and goes ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
(ooh)
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way love goes ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
[Vocalization]
♪ Don't you know, oh,
that's the way ♪
♪ That's the way ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's the way ♪
♪ [Deep Voice Singer]
That's the way ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's the way ♪
♪ [Deep Voice Singer]
That's the way ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's the way ♪
♪ [Deep Voice Singer]
That's the way ♪
♪ That's the way love
goes, and goes, and goes ♪
♪ [Deep Voice Singer]
That's the way ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
(scatting)
♪ That's the way love goes, oh ♪
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
♪ [Male Singer] That's
the way love goes ♪
♪ [Male Singer]
That's the way love ♪
♪ [Deep Voice Singer]
♪ [Male Singer]
That's the way love ♪
♪ [Deep Voice Singer]
♪ That's the way love goes ♪
(laughing) (clapping)
- [Woman] You came with it
- Tish, don't look
into the camera, dang!
Why you gotta look
into the camera?
(group complaining)
- All night, been
messing everything up
(group chatter)
- [Woman] We give
you some props!
(laughter)
- [Woman] Tryin'a be sexy.
(loud laughter)
Na, but d'you see
her tryin'a be sexy?
- [Man] I know!